Salvador Hernández López

Full Stack Developer

If something I don't know, I'll look into it and I will.

Areas of Knowledge

Laravel I've created project with Laravel framework using the MVC Laravel tools and the testing tools.

ReactJs I fully know how to use both the props and class components, stateless functional components, hook components and Redux.

Angular I master using the components of this framework and I alway try to take advantage of the angular materials to have good UI results.

NodeJs I used to develop web apps using NodeJS Express and Jade. But, nowadays I've tended to make API rests in order to make MEAN stack apps and MERN stack apps.

Docker I've created container and images using docker and docker-compose to develop and deploy projects.

Git I've used git, git-flow as version control system and github, gitlab and bitbucket to team work.

Java I have a lot of experience coding in Java since I've worked with it for a long time. I know how to make either CLI apps, GUI apps and web apps.

Data bases I start modeling using CASE tools and then I implement them in MySQL , MariaDB or SQLServer.

Software I'm able to make software engineering that goes from requirements analysis using engineering case tools.

Professional Experience

2018-Present **Web developer**, *The Software Artisans*, Morelia Mich.

Under this period on TSA I've developed web solutions used differents tools for example NodeJS, Laravel, Angular etc. and I've trained to the new people in TSA.

2020 Web developer, XML Team Solutions, LLC.

I've developed a CRUD web application using Laravel and docker.

2017–2018 **Developer and tester**, *Instituto Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de Zamora*. I created multiples modules to CRUD web application using PHP

Education

2014–2018 **Computerstystems Engineer**, Instituto Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de Zamora, Zamora Mich., Final Grade .

Languages

Spanish native

English Intermediate

Hobbies

- o Calisthenics
- o Video Games
- o Reading books
- o Playing guitar